Guide to the Records of The New York Institute for the Humanities RG.37.4
New York University Archives
- Series III: Audio Recordings, 67170
  - Subseries A: Cassette Tapes, 1974-2005; 67171
    - Beard Conference Tape 2, 22-Jan-82; cuid3733; 67553 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Beard Conference Tape 3, 22-Jan-82; cuid3734; 67552 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Beard Conference Tape 4, 22-Jan-82; cuid3735; 67551 (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Richard Sennett, Democracy and Urban Form, 26-Feb-82; cuid3736; 67550 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Sex, Genders and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 28-Jan-82; cuid3737; 67549 (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Allen Hunter on the New Right, 29-Jan-82; cuid3738; 67548 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82; cuid3739; 67547 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Taste Seminar, Denis Altman Tape 1, 3-Mar-82; cuid3740; 67546 (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 1, 11-Feb-82; cuid3741; 67545 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Defert Symposium Tape 2, 11-Feb-82; cuid3742; 67544 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Defert Lunch, 12-Feb-82; cuid3743; 67543 (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Censorship Seminar, 25-Feb-82; cuid3744; 67542 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - John Leonard, Censorship Seminar, 11-Mar-82; cuid3745; 67541 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 1, 12-Mar-82; cuid3746; 67540 (Box 40, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273576
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York and International Economics Tape 2, 12-Mar-82; cuid3747; 67539 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - Linda Nochlin, Problems in Biography of Artists, 19-Mar-82; cuid3748; 67538 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - New Right Seminar 1, 20-Mar-82; cuid3749; 67537 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - New Right Seminar 2, 20-Mar-82; cuid3750; 67536 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - New Right Seminar 3, 20-Mar-82; cuid3751; 67535 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Monique Wittig, 26-Mar-82; cuid3752; 67534 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Tomas Venclova, Censorship Seminar, 1-Apr-82; cuid3753; 67533 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Edmund White, Trios, 19-Apr-82; cuid3754; 67532 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Bob Darnton, Censorship Seminar, 22-Apr-82; cuid3755; 67531 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Moshe Safdie Lecture, 25-Apr-82; cuid3756; 67530 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Censorship Seminar - Pornography, 13-May-82; cuid3757; 67529 (Box 41, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273584
    - Women, War and Feminism, 14-May-82; cuid3758; 67528 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Ewa Kuryluk Luncheon, 28-May-82; cuid3759; 67527 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - H. Gans, Censorship Seminar "Self-Censorship", 4-Jun-82; cuid3760; 67526 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - "Independent Thought in Hungary" by Gyorgy Bence, 12-Jul-82; cuid3761; 67525 (Box 41, Folder 5)
      Access copy available on 2 CDs: ACCESS 11:15 and ACCESS 11:16
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 1, 13-Sep-82; cuid3762; 67524 (Box 42, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273592
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism Session 2, 20-Sep-82; cuid3763; 67523 (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, On Borges, 24-Sep-82; cuid3764; 67522 (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 1, 24-Sep-82; cuid3765; 67521 (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - William Leach, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 24-Sep-82; cuid3766; 67520 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - New Right Tape 2, 25-Sep-82; cuid3767; 67519 (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 4-Oct-82; cuid3768; 67518 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 1, 5-Oct-82; cuid3769; 67517 (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City Tape 2, 5-Oct-82; cuid3770; 67516 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Abel Decaux. Debussy - Chansons de Bilitis, 11-Oct-82; cuid3771; 67515 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 11-Oct-82; cuid3772; 67514 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Lawrence Pitkethly, Visual History, 14-Oct-83; cuid3773; 67513 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Nadine Gordimer, Fellows Lunch, 15-Oct-82; 2018-02; cuid471; 67512 (Box 42, Folder 13, Cassette cuid471, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records nyuarchives_rg37.4_cuid471, Box Access 15, Cd rg37.4_cuid471)
      Original Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Duration: 58 min.
    - Richard Howard, 18-Oct-82; cuid3774; 67511 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, New York City, 19-Oct-82; cuid3775; 67510 (Box 43, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273600
    - Nicholas Wahl Tape 2, 22-Oct-82; cuid3776; 67509 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 25-Oct-82; cuid3777; 67508 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - T. Spires J.Coleman, Borges Seminar, 27-Oct-82; cuid3778; 67507 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Judith Wexler, 29-Oct-82; cuid3779; 67506 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Pre-Modernism, 1-Nov-82; cuid3780; 67505 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - T. Nagel, The Mind-Body Problem, 5-Nov-82; cuid3781; 67504 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Charles Halpern, CUNY Queens School of Law, 12-Nov-82; cuid3782; 67503 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 1, 6-Nov-82; cuid3783; 67502 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Amartya Sen Lunch Tape 2, 16-Nov-82; cuid3784; 67501 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 1, 3-Dec-82; cuid3785; 67500 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture Tape 2, 3-Dec-82; cuid3786; 67499 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 1, 14-Dec-82; cuid3787; 67498 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 2, 14-Dec-82; cuid3788; 67497 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - New Right Seminar Tape 3, 14-Dec-82; cuid3789; 67496 (Box 44, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273618
    - George Soros, 10-Dec-82; cuid3790; 67495 (Box 44, Folder 2)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 11:18
    - Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture, 17-Dec-82; cuid3791; 67494 (Box 44, Folder 3)
    - William Leach, Sexuality and Consumerism, 14-Jan-83; cuid3792; 67493 (Box 44, Folder 4)
    - Richard Howard, Ante-Modernism, 21-Jan-83; cuid3793; 67492 (Box 44, Folder 5)
    - Richard Howard, Ante-Modernism, 21-Jan-83; cuid3794; 67491 (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - George Soros, International Financial Crisis, 4-Feb-83; cuid3795; 67490 (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Richard Martin, Consumer culture - Fashion, 25-Feb-83; cuid3796; 67489 (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Joan Wallach Scott, Gender and Work, 25-Mar-83; cuid3797; 67488 (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - Brodsky, Heaney, Walcott - Fellows Lunch, 4-Mar-83; cuid3798; 67487 (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Jerome bruner Lunch - On Language, 11-Mar-83; cuid3799; 67486 (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - Richard Sennett, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Promiscuity, 11-Mar-83; cuid3800; 67485 (Box 44, Folder 12)
    - Workplace Seminar Tape 1, 15-Mar-83; cuid3801; 67484 (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - Workplace Seminar Tape 2, 15-Mar-83; cuid3802; 67483 (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - Aryeh Neier on Human Rights, 18-Mar-83; cuid3803; 67482 (Box 45, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273626
    - Anti-Modernism and Modernism, 25-Mar-83; cuid3804; 67481 (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Jackson Lears, Advertising and Consumer Culture, 25-Mar-83; cuid3805; 67480 (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Jackson Lears, Advertising and Consumer Culture, 25-Mar-83; cuid3806; 67479 (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Italo Calvino Lunch, 1-Apr-83; cuid3807; 67478 (Box 45, Folder 5, Box Access 13, Item 57)
    - Hatch/Sassen-Koob, 6-Apr-83; cuid3808; 67477 (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Searle, Putnam, Boyd, 8-Apr-83; cuid3809; 67476 (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Haskell, 15-Apr-83; cuid3810; 67475 (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Confessions of an Activist Mogul, 21-Apr-83; cuid3811; 67474 (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Sharon Thompson, Teenage Girls and Sexuality, 22-Apr-83; cuid3812; 67473 (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Sharon Thompson, Teenage Girls and Sexuality, 22-Apr-83; cuid3813; 67472 (Box 45, Folder 11)
    - Stankiewicz Lunch, 29-Apr-83; cuid3814; 67471 (Box 45, Folder 12)
    - Luisa Velenzuela, Politics in Argentina, 20-May-83; cuid3815; 67470 (Box 45, Folder 13)
    - Hatch Tape 2, 8-Jun-83; cuid3816; 67469 (Box 45, Folder 14)
    - Hatch Tape 3, 8-Jun-83; cuid3817; 67468 (Box 45, Folder 15)
    - Derek Walcott, Narrative Seminar, 6-May-83; cuid3818; 67467 (Box 46, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273634
    - T. Kaplan, "The Left's Influence of Catholics", 30-Sep-83; cuid3819; 67466 (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Sir Stuart Hampshire, 6-Oct-83; cuid3820; 67465 (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - Sir Stuart Hampshire, "History of Conflict", 7-Oct-83; cuid3821; 67464 (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - A Tribute to W.H. Auden, Guggenheim Museum, 18-Oct-83; cuid3822; 67463 (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Frank Kermode Lunch, Biblical Interpretation, 28-Oct-83; cuid3823; 67462 (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Noel Annan, "How Should We Direct Shakespeare", 10-Oct-83; cuid3824; 67461 (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, 14-Nov-83; cuid3825; 67460 (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Richard Howard Lunch, on Gide, 18-Nov-83; cuid3826; 67459 (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, 30-Nov-83; cuid3827; 67458 (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Natalie Zemon Davis, Fellows Lunch, 2-Dec-83; cuid3828; 67457 (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - William Weaver, "Verdi's Taste", 8-Dec-83; cuid3829; 67456 (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - William Weaver, "Verdi's Taste", 9-Dec-83; cuid3830; 67455 (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Friday Lunch/ Program Committee, 11-Jan-84; cuid3831; 67454 (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - John Guare and Peter Brooks, Narrative Seminar, 8-Jan-84; cuid3832; 67453 (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Richard Sennett, The Decline of Political Fiction, 20-Jan-84; cuid3833; 67452 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273642
    - Stan Eckstut, Learning from New York City, 10-Feb-84; cuid3834; 67451 (Box 47, Folder 2)
    - Yehudi Menuhin Lecture, 14-Feb-84; cuid3835; 67450 (Box 47, Folder 3)
    - J. Hillis Miller Literary Criticism and Verification, 24-Feb-84; cuid3836; 67449 (Box 47, Folder 4)
    - Quentin Anderson, "Two Responses to a Consumer World", 2-Mar-84; cuid3837; 67448 (Box 47, Folder 5)
    - Alfred Kazin Lunch, 22-Mar-84; 2018-2; cuid472; 67447 (Box 47, Folder 6, Cassette cuid472, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records nyuarchives_rg37.4_cuid472_000001, E-records nyuarchives_rg37.4_cuid472_000002, Box Access 15, Item 26)
      Original Format: 1/8" audiocassette, Duration: 60 min.
      Housing Annotations
      Tape label reads, "Alfred Kazin Lunch 'The Crucial Century of American Writing'"
    - Aryeh Neier Lunch, "Human Rights Abuses in South America", 23-Mar-84; cuid3838; 67446 (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - George Konrad Lunch, "The Dilemmas of a New Novel", 30-Mar-84; cuid3839; 67445 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      Access copy available on CD: ACCESS 11:17
    - David Reiff, Translation Seminar, 3-Apr-84; cuid3840; 67444 (Box 47, Folder 9)
    - Bill Leach Lunch, "Color, Glass and Light in New York City Department Stores", 6-Apr-84; cuid3841; 67443 (Box 47, Folder 10)
    - Richard Sennett, Narrative Seminar, 15-Apr-83; cuid3842; 67442 (Box 47, Folder 11)
    - Translation Seminar, 16-Apr-84; cuid3843; 67441 (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - David Reiff, Translation Seminar, 16-Apr-84; cuid3844; 67440 (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - David Kalstone, Narrating and Describing, 11-May-84; cuid3845; 67439 (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - David Kalstone, Narrating and Describing, 11-May-84; cuid3846; 67438 (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Maurice Berger, "The Empty Frame: Pictorial Realism", 18-May-84; cuid3847; 67437 (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - R. Howard, Translation Seminar, 18-May-84; cuid3848; 67436 (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Carol Smith Rosenberg, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - The Body Politic, 12-Oct-84; cuid3849; 67435 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273659
    - Father Ong, Institute Lunch, 12-Oct-84; cuid3850; 67434 (Box 48, Folder 2)
    - Jerome Bruner Lunch, Narrative and Paradigmatic Modes, 19-Oct-84; cuid3851; 67433 (Box 48, Folder 3)
    - Jerome Bruner and Richard Howard, Narrative Seminar, 23-Oct-84; cuid3852; 67432 (Box 48, Folder 4)
    - Sally Stein, Gender and Consumerism - Ladies Home Journal, 26-Oct-84; cuid3853; 67431 (Box 48, Folder 5)
    - Peter Buckley, Theatre and the Public, 26-Oct-84; cuid3854; 67430 (Box 48, Folder 6)
    - Tom Bishop, Narrative Seminar, 6-Nov-84; cuid3855; 67429 (Box 48, Folder 7)
    - Eric Hobsbawm, Literacy and the Tower of Babel, 9-Nov-84; cuid3856; 67428 (Box 48, Folder 8, Box Digitized Access Files, File rg37.4_cuid3856)
    - Lourdes Aguello and Ruby Rich, Sex and Gender - Repression of Homosexuality in Cuba, 9-Nov-84; cuid3857; 67427 (Box 48, Folder 9)
    - Aryeh Neier, Friday Lunch, 16-Nov-84; cuid3858; 67426 (Box 48, Folder 10)
    - Narrative Seminar, 11-Dec-84; cuid3859; 67425 (Box 48, Folder 11)
    - E.L. Doctorow, 18-Jan-85; cuid3860; 67424 (Box 48, Folder 12)
    - Oliver Sacks, Clinical Biography, 22-Jan-85; cuid3861; 67423 (Box 48, Folder 13)
    - Saskia Sassen-Koob, Foreign Investments in the U.S., 25-Jan-85; cuid3862; 67422 (Box 48, Folder 14)
    - John Coleman, Narrative Coleman, 5-Feb-85; cuid3863; 67421 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273667
    - Thomas Bishop, Performance to Text, 15-Feb-85; cuid3864; 67420 (Box 49, Folder 2)
    - David Reiff and Ted Mooney, Travel, 19-Feb-85; cuid3865; 67419 (Box 49, Folder 3)
    - Vicki Hearne, Tracking Dogs and Traces of Speech, 22-Feb-85; cuid3866; 67418 (Box 49, Folder 4)
    - Carol Gilligan, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 15-Mar-85; cuid3867; 67417 (Box 49, Folder 5)
    - Galway Kinnell, Problems of Writing, 1-Mar-85; cuid3868; 67416 (Box 49, Folder 6)
    - Atina Grossman, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 29-Mar-85; cuid3869; 67415 (Box 49, Folder 7)
    - Emily Honig and Gail Hershatter, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 12-Apr-85; cuid3870; 67414 (Box 49, Folder 8)
    - Tony Quinton Lunch, 19-Apr-85; cuid3871; 67413 (Box 49, Folder 9)
    - Betty Fussell, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - on Cookbooks and Food, 26-Apr-85; cuid3872; 67412 (Box 49, Folder 10)
    - Leo Bersani, 2-May-85; cuid3873; 67411 (Box 49, Folder 11)
    - Leo Bersani - Follow-up lecture, 3-May-85; cuid3874; 67410 (Box 49, Folder 12)
    - Lisa Duggan, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 10-May-85; cuid3875; 67409 (Box 49, Folder 13)
    - Faye Ginsburg, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Right to Life Women, 24-May-85; cuid3876; 67408 (Box 49, Folder 14)
    - Nicholas Wahl, Friday Lunch - "Kundera's Europe: The Illusion of Westernity", 11-Nov-85; cuid3877; 67407 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273675
    - Chris Stansall, Sex - Gender, 11-Oct-85; cuid3878; 67406 (Box 50, Folder 2)
    - Bert Hansen, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 25-Oct-85; cuid3879; 67405 (Box 50, Folder 3)
    - Michael Scammel, Emigration of the Arts from the Soviet Union, 25-Oct-85; cuid669; 67404 (Box 50, Cassette cuid669, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records cuid669, Box Access 16, Disk 17)
      1/8" audiocassette, 76 min.
      Preservation Note: Side 1: 00:34:03;xx - 00:37:30;xx [end] and all of side 2: O-Extremely poor audio quality - static break up throughout - much of it is unintelligible.
    - Mark Girouard, To See and Be Seen Tape 1, 31-Oct-85; cuid3880; 67403 (Box 50, Folder 5)
    - Mark Girouard, To See and Be Seen Tape 2, 31-Oct-85; cuid3881; 67402 (Box 50, Folder 6)
    - Mark Girouard Follow-up Lecture, 1-Nov-85; cuid3882; 67401 (Box 50, Folder 7)
    - George Chauncey II, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Sex Panics, 1-Nov-85; cuid3883; 67400 (Box 50, Folder 8)
    - Jeff Weinstein and Betty Fussel, Sex, Gender, 22-Nov-85; cuid3884; 67399 (Box 50, Folder 9)
    - Luisa Valenzuela, Argentina, Cannibals and Poets, 6-Dec-85; cuid3885; 67398 (Box 50, Folder 10)
    - Kate Ellis, Sex, Gender and Consumerism- Eating Disorders, 6-Dec-85; cuid3886; 67397 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - Sex, Gender and Consumerism, "The Auto-Eroticism of Driving", 20-Dec-85; cuid3887; 67396 (Box 50, Folder 12)
    - Peggy Davis, "Watching Judges Make the Law", 31-Dec-85; cuid3888; 67395 (Box 50, Folder 13)
    - Breyten Breytenbach, Friday Lunch - New Poems, 17-Jan-86; cuid3889; 67394 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273683
    - Miriam Hansen, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - On Valentino, 31-Jan-86; cuid3890; 67393 (Box 51, Folder 2)
    - Thomas Bender, Lunch, 31-Jan-86; cuid3891; 67392 (Box 51, Folder 3)
    - Richard Sennett, Lunch - Reading from his new novel, 14-Feb-86; cuid3892; 67391 (Box 51, Folder 4)
    - Anthony Heilbut, culture and Economics, 21-Feb-86; cuid3893; 67390 (Box 51, Folder 5)
    - Mary Nash, Lunch - Spanish and Portuguese, 7-Mar-86; cuid3894; 67389 (Box 51, Folder 6)
    - S. Bowles, American Culture, 21-Mar-86; cuid3895; 67388 (Box 51, Folder 7)
    - John Coleman, Friday Lunch - Thinking About Singing, 4-Apr-86; cuid3896; 67387 (Box 51, Folder 8)
    - Eugenia Zukerman, Friday Lunch - For Flute Only, 18-Apr-86; cuid3897; 67386 (Box 51, Folder 9)
    - M. Sinha, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 16-May-85; cuid3898; 67385 (Box 51, Folder 10)
    - Judy Walkowitz, Sex, Gender and Consumerism - Victorian Melodrama, 30-May-86; cuid3899; 67384 (Box 51, Folder 11)
    - Richard Poirier, 11-Oct-86; cuid3900; 67383 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273691
    - Kate Stimpson, Sex, Gender and Consumer Culture - Kate Stimpson on Representation, 24-Oct-86; cuid3901; 67382 (Box 52, Folder 2)
    - Aryeh Neier, 25-Oct-86; cuid3902; 67381 (Box 52, Folder 3)
    - Gerald Holton, Nov-86; cuid3903; 67380 (Box 52, Folder 4)
    - Laura Mulvey, Sex, Gender and Consumerism, 7-Nov-86; cuid3904; 67379 (Box 52, Folder 5)
    - Roger Strauss Lunch, Frankfurt Book Fair, 7-Nov-86; cuid3905; 67378 (Box 52, Folder 6)
    - Dan Czitrom, 21-Nov-86; cuid3906; 67377 (Box 52, Folder 7)
    - Commercial Culture Seminar, 5-Dec-86; cuid3907; 67376 (Box 52, Folder 8)
    - Holton, Donoghue, bruner, 8-Dec-86; cuid3908; 67375 (Box 52, Folder 9)
    - The Question of Progress in Science and the Humanities Tape II, 8-Dec-86; cuid3909; 67374 (Box 52, Folder 10)
    - Peter Buckley, 30-Jan-87; cuid3910; 67373 (Box 52, Folder 11)
    - Oliver Sacks on Darwin, 1987; 2018-02; cuid473; 67372 (Box 52, Folder 12, Cassette cuid473, Box Digitized Access Files, E-records nyuarchives_rg37.4_cuid473_000001, Box Access 15, Cd rg37.4_cuid473_000001, Cd rg37.4_cuid473_000002)
      Original Format: 1/8" Audiocassette, Duration: 95 min.
      Housing Annotations:
      Tape label reads, "Oliver Sacks on Darwin; Travel Seminar"
    - Inventing Times Square, Developing A Place, 28-Oct-88; cuid3911; 67371 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273709
    - "I Giullari di Piazza", "Dea Fortuna" Demo Tape, 9-Dec-88; cuid3912; 67370 (Box 53, Folder 2)
    - Katha Pollitt, 3-Mar-89; cuid3913; 67369 (Box 53, Folder 3)
    - Senelick, 3-Mar-89; cuid3914; 67368 (Box 53, Folder 4)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 1, 3-Mar-89; cuid3915; 67367 (Box 53, Folder 5)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 2, 3-Mar-89; cuid3916; 67366 (Box 53, Folder 6)
    - D'Ag Faculty Club Tape 3, 3-Mar-89; cuid3917; 67365 (Box 53, Folder 7)
    - Snow Dining Room Tape 1, 14-Apr-89; cuid3918; 67364 (Box 53, Folder 8)
    - Snow Dining Room Tape 1, 14-Apr-89; cuid3919; 67363 (Box 53, Folder 9)
    - Steering Committee Meeting, 29-Apr-89; cuid3920; 67362 (Box 53, Folder 10)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/3, 21-Mar-91; cuid3921; 67361 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273717
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/3, 21-Mar-91; cuid3922; 67360 (Box 54, Folder 2)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 3/3, 21-Mar-91; cuid3923; 67359 (Box 54, Folder 3)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 21-Mar-91; cuid3924; 67358 (Box 54, Folder 4)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 21-Mar-91; cuid3925; 67357 (Box 54, Folder 5)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 21-Mar-91; cuid3926; 67356 (Box 54, Folder 6)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 21-Mar-91; cuid3927; 67355 (Box 54, Folder 7)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91; cuid3928; 67354 (Box 54, Folder 8)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 22-Mar-91; cuid3929; 67353 (Box 54, Folder 9)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91; cuid3930; 67352 (Box 54, Folder 10)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 22-Mar-91; cuid3931; 67351 (Box 54, Folder 11)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 22-Mar-91; cuid3932; 67350 (Box 54, Folder 12)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/3, 22-Mar-91; cuid3933; 67349 (Box 54, Folder 13)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 1/2, 23-Mar-91; cuid3934; 67348 (Box 54, Folder 14)
    - NYU - NYIH Am 2/2, 23-Mar-91; cuid3935; 67347 (Box 54, Folder 15)
    - Michael Wood, "On a Sentence By Proust" Tape 1, 15-Oct-93; cuid3936; 67346 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273725
    - Michael Wood, "On a Sentence By Proust" Tape 2, 15-Oct-93; cuid3937; 67345 (Box 55, Folder 2)
    - A. Richard Turner, Adam Gopnik, "Art History: The Last Press of the Grape?" Tape 1, )ct 22, 1993; cuid3938; 67344 (Box 55, Folder 3)
    - A. Richard Turner, Adam Gopnik, "Art History: The Last Press of the Grape?" Tape 2, )ct 22, 1993; cuid3939; 67343 (Box 55, Folder 4)
    - Ronald Dworkin, "Rationing, Justice and the Clinton Health Care Plan", 5-Nov-93; cuid3940; 67342 (Box 55, Folder 5)
    - Eva Hoffman, "Exit Into History: A Journey Through the New Eastern Europe", 12-Nov-93; cuid3941; 67341 (Box 55, Folder 6)
    - Martha Nussbaum, "Platonic Love and Colorado Law", 19-Nov-93; cuid3942; 67340 (Box 55, Folder 7)
    - Bruce Bawer and Paul Berman, "A Dialogue About Gay History", 18-Feb-94; cuid3943; 67339 (Box 55, Folder 8)
    - Lucy McDiarmid, "Roger Casement and Modern Irish Memory", 4-Mar-94; cuid3944; 67338 (Box 55, Folder 9)
    - Lucy McDiarmid, "Roger Casement and Modern Irish Memory" - Copy, 4-Mar-94; cuid3945; 67337 (Box 55, Folder 10)
    - Andrew Delbanco at Deutsches Haus - master, 25-Mar-94; cuid3946; 67336 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273733
    - Andrew Delbanco at Deutsches Haus - copy, 25-Mar-94; cuid3947; 67335 (Box 56, Folder 2)
    - Dennis Hollier at Deutsches Haus - master, 1-Apr-94; cuid3948; 67334 (Box 56, Folder 3)
    - Dennis Hollier at Deutsches Haus - copy, 1-Apr-94; cuid3949; 67333 (Box 56, Folder 4)
    - Francesca Dow at Deutsches Haus, 8-Apr-94; cuid3950; 67332 (Box 56, Folder 5)
    - Alfred Kazin, at Deutsches Haus, 15-Apr-94; cuid3951; 67331 (Box 56, Folder 6)
    - Alfred Kazin, "Writing is All: Life as a Critic", 15-Apr-94; cuid3952; 67330 (Box 56, Folder 7)
    - Nicholas Lemann, "The American Meritocracy" - master, 22-Apr-94; cuid3953; 67329 (Box 56, Folder 8)
    - Nicholas Lemann, "The American Meritocracy" - copy, 22-Apr-94; cuid3954; 67328 (Box 56, Folder 9)
    - Paul Muldoon, "A Reading of His Poetry", 29-Apr-94; cuid3955; 67327 (Box 56, Folder 10)
    - Simon Schama, 7-Oct-94; cuid3956; 67326 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273741
    - German House Tape 1, 14-Oct-94; cuid3957; 67325 (Box 57, Folder 2)
    - German House Tape 1, 21-Oct-94; cuid3958; 67324 (Box 57, Folder 3)
    - Melissa Roberts, 28-Oct-94; cuid3959; 67323 (Box 57, Folder 4)
    - Fritz Stern, 18-Nov-94; cuid3960; 67322 (Box 57, Folder 5)
    - Jos Rose, 2-Dec-94; cuid3961; 67321 (Box 57, Folder 6)
    - Kurt Andersen, 9-Dec-94; cuid3962; 67320 (Box 57, Folder 7)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 3-Mar-95; cuid3963; 67319 (Box 57, Folder 8)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 10-Mar-95; cuid3964; 67318 (Box 57, Folder 9)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 17-Mar-95; cuid3965; 67317 (Box 57, Folder 10)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 31-Mar-95; cuid3966; 67316 (Box 57, Folder 11)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 14-Apr-95; cuid3967; 67315 (Box 57, Folder 12)
    - Jocelyn Carlson Baltzell, 21-Apr-95; cuid3968; 67314 (Box 57, Folder 13)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 1, 14-Jun-95; cuid3969; 67313 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      barcode#:31142042273758
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 2, 14-Jun-95; cuid3970; 67312 (Box 58, Folder 2)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 3, 14-Jun-95; cuid3971; 67311 (Box 58, Folder 3)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 4, 14-Jun-95; cuid3972; 67310 (Box 58, Folder 4)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5a, 15-Jun-95; cuid3973; 67309 (Box 58, Folder 5)
    - Conference on Cities in North America Tape 5b, 15-Jun-95; cuid3974; 67308 (Box 58, Folder 6)